schoolanduniversity.com 2012-10-12

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting schoolanduniversity.com (referred to in this privacy policy as the Site), which is owned and operated by SchoolandUniversity Inc., (throughout the privacy policy referred to as SchoolandUniversity Inc, us, our, or we). SchoolandUniversity Inc takes privacy and transparency very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be collected and treated as you make full use of the Site. 

Site Restricted to Individuals over the Age of 18 It is our intent only to collect personally identifiable information from individuals who are at least 18 years of age, who are legal residents of the United States with a legitimate email and mailing address, and who voluntarily provide such information by completing the registration process on the Site or by completing one or more forms on the site requesting information or services from us. If you fail to meet any of the age, email or mailing address requirements described above, you are not permitted to complete the registration process or any forms on the Site that request personally identifiable information. 

**What the Privacy Policy Covers**  
By using the Site you are consenting to the terms of this privacy policy explained below and representing to us that you meet the age, email, and mailing address restrictions described above. We believe in permission-based marketing, and therefore have described below the information we collect from you and how that information is used by us and others. Specifically this policy explains how we treat Personal Information (information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, email address, phone number, and age that may not otherwise be publicly available) that we collect when you (i) visit the Site, (ii) accept, sign up for, or request any of our, or our Affiliates’ or advertisers’, offers or services, or (iii) use or buy any goods or services we market. This privacy policy also controls use of information related to your previous use of the Site, our products, and our services. Affiliates includes any business which is a subsidiary of SchoolandUniversity Inc or under common ownership or control with SchoolandUniversity Inc. 

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  
We accumulate Personal Information when you choose to provide us various types of personally identifiable information through various means which may include, but are not limited to, responding to a direct marketing advertisement from us, submitting content in connection with a contest we are hosting, participating in interactive online activities through the Site or our Affiliates’ websites such as responding to questions and surveys, posting community listings, providing ratings, conducting searches and comparison searches, bidding, purchasing, chatting, playing games, entering contests, posting on bulletin boards, etc. We collect this Personal Information when you manually enter it into any online form available on the Site or an Affiliates’ website. In order for you to take full advantage of the Site, we encourage you to provide your Personal Information to us. Providing your Personal Information is, however, voluntary. You may choose not to provide us with your Personal Information by simply not entering it on the Site or any Affiliates’ website. However, if you do not provide us with your Personal Information, we may not be able to provide you certain services. 

**Anonymous Information and Cookies**  
If you do not provide us any of your Personal Information, we are limited in the information we may collect from you. For example, we may be able to determine your IP address for the purposes of administering the Site and tracking Site usage. However, your IP address may vary each time you visit or it may remain the same depending on the type of Internet connection you are using or the location from which you access the Site. We may also collect information about the websites that directed you to the Site after you clicked on a text or banner link or an ad from another website, or the day and time you visited the Site and how long you spent on the Site. We aggregate such information to help us to compile reports as to trends and other behavior about users visiting our Site; however such information is anonymous and cannot be tied directly to you.  
We may also use cookies and your Personal Information to enhance your experience on the Site and to provide you with personalized offers. A cookie is a small data file placed on your computer’s hard drive that contains information that allows us to track your activity on the Site. The cookie itself does not contain any Personal Information; however, if you provide us any Personal Information the cookie may act as an identifier to tie your Personal Information to your IP address or computer. You may choose to delete cookies from your computer’s hard drive at anytime or to disable cookies on your computer. If you delete cookies that relate to the Site, we may not be able to identify you upon your return to the Site. Additionally, if you disable your computer’s cookies, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site that require that cookies be enabled. The Site’s cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. Additionally, our cookies cannot be used as a virus, Trojan horse, worm, or any other malicious tool that could impair your use of your computer. Our cookies are used to help us better understand how you and other users use the Site so we can continue to provide a better, more personalized user experience on the Site. We also share website usage information about our Site with those interested in running targeted promotional campaigns on the Site. For this purpose, we and our advertisers track some of the pages that you visit on the Site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs).

**Why We Collect Information**  
We collect anonymous and Personal Information about you to provide you the most relevant information, products, programs, and services that you request; to constantly improve the features, offerings, and content that we provide through the Site; to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to determine how you use and respond to the features, offerings, and advertisements on the Site; to provide you with advertising and offerings from our Affiliates or advertising partners targeted to your preferences; and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may interest you. We reserve the right to collect and reuse the anonymous and Personal Information about you for marketing purposes.

**Sharing and Disclosing Your Information for Commercial Purposes**  
If you register with us by completing one or more of the offers on the Site you understand that you will be concurrently registered with our Affiliates and advertising partners and that we may share your Personal Information with third-party companies who intend to use the information for their marketing purposes. Personal Information we obtain from you during your registration remains your property, but by registering for one or more offers on the Site or otherwise sharing your Personal Information with us, you grant us the right to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes including, but not limited to, sharing such information via co-registration with Affiliates and advertising partners (i.e., by clicking on any advertiser’s banner you agree to be co-registered at that advertiser’s website at zero cost to you). Additionally, we may sell and/or license your Personal Information to third-party businesses who deem the offers you have completed particularly relevant to their business. These businesses may include, but are not limited to, educational institutions and direct marketing providers. 

**Sharing Your Information with Our Service Providers**  
We hire other service providers to execute specific functions on our behalf. Examples include conducting marketing campaigns via email, direct mail, telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, removing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. While performing these services, our service providers may have access to your Personal Information as needed to complete their functions for us.

**Other Instances When We Use or Share Your Information**  
We may also use your information to deliver offers you have requested, to carry out contests, track your observance to Site rules, to assess how to improve the Site’s content, and to receive feedback. We reserve the right, on behalf of ourselves and our Affiliates, to release your information in the event that  
(i) we believe you have used the Site in violation of the Site’s rules or to carry out unlawful acts,  
(ii) the information is subpoenaed or otherwise required to mitigate our liability in a lawsuit or other legal process,  
(iii) SchoolandUniversity Inc or one of its Affiliates, is sold, acquired, or merged with another company, or substantially all of our assets or the assets of one of our Affiliates are acquired, or   
(iv) when we deem it essential or appropriate. To the degree that we acquire your credit card information, that information will be kept confidential and will not be shared with any third parties without your prior informed consent. Notwithstanding our commitment to keep your credit card information confidential, we reserve the right to share with third parties the fact that we have your credit card information on file.

**Opting Out**  
This privacy policy describes the potential ways we might share your information. If you do not agree to our potential uses of your Personal Information as we have described in this privacy policy, you are not required to provide your Personal Information to us. However, once your Personal Information is shared with us and we share that information with third parties, we and they may send you direct marketing advertisements, or include you in our respective email, direct mail, telemarketing, or SMS text-message marketing campaigns. All third parties with whom we share your Personal Information are bound by the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. 7701, et seq.) and the National Do-Not-Call Registry and are obligated to be in complete compliance with all consumer opt-out rules and policies. If at any time you would like to stop receiving offers from any of our Affiliates or a third party, please contact the Affiliate or third party directly and ask them to remove you from their marketing campaigns or visit their website for complete details as to how you may unsubscribe from their campaigns. If you do not want to receive email, direct mail, telemarketing, or SMS text-messaging from us, please let us know by emailing info@schoolanduniversity.com.

**Privacy on Third-Party Websites**  
Our Site contains links to third-party websites. This privacy policy only covers our use of your information that we collect through the Site. The websites of advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party websites accessible through the Site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. As such, we urge you to review their respective privacy policies when visiting third-party websites.

**Transferability of Information**  
Information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy by us may be stored and processed within the United States of America or in any other country in which we or our agents maintain facilities. By using our Web site, you consent to any transfer of Personal Information outside of your country, should we find it necessary. Security of Your Information Within our company your Personal Information may only be accessed on a need to know basis by employees who must access that information to supply products or services to you to do their jobs and to fulfill on requests that you have made through the Site. Additionally, we have instituted physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet federal regulations to protect your Personal Information. However, there is a slight chance that Internet transmissions containing your Personal Information may be intercepted by others. There is no way for us to ensure the privacy of your information before it arrives at the Site or after it leaves the Site.  
By using any part of the Site, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this privacy policy as it may be amended and updated from time to time. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, please do not use the Site.When you supply us your Personal Information through the Site or through any link or form that directs you to the Site, you agree to be contacted and/or to receive offers from schoolanduniversity.com, its Affiliates, or our third-party advertisers, and that we may use and share your Personal Information as outlined above. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to amend this privacy policy at any time, so please check back to the Site and this privacy policy frequently to be aware of and understand all updates. All changes to the privacy policy will be effective immediately upon their publication to the Site. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted, the changes to the amended or revised privacy policy by your continued use of the Site. 

Effective as of July 17, 2012  
Contact Information :  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or to legal issues pertaining to the Site or your use of the Site, please contact us: info@schoolanduniversity.com [ ](http://www.schoolanduniversity.com/request-information)
